sarugbymag.co.za 2018-05-02

# 

### PRIVACY POLICY

THIS PRIVACY POLICY (“POLICY”) GOVERNS THE COLLECTION,  
MANAGEMENT AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT  
HIGHBURY MEDIA (PTY) LTD (“HM,” “we” OR “us”) COLLECTS THROUGH  
THE FOLLOWING WEBSITES:  
http://www.dash4cash.com  
http://www.sarugbymagazine.com  
http://www.capetownetc.com  
http://www.weddingalbum.co.za  
http://www.sacricketmag.com  
http://www.sasoccermag.co.za  
http://www.sportsclub.co.za  
http://aa.co.za  
http://www.compleatgolfer.co.za  
http://www.mykitchen.co.za  
("THE WEBSITES").  
WE RESPECT YOUR RIGHTS TO RESPONSIBLE MANAGEMENT OF  
YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION UNDER THE PROTECTION OF  
PERSONAL INFORMATION ACT 4 OF 2013. YOUR USE OF THE  
WEBSITES AND HM'S PRODUCTS AND SERVICES IS SUBJECT TO THIS  
POLICY. BY USING THE WEBSITES, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR CONSENT TO  
PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE  
WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY TERM  
IN THIS POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS WEBSITES OR SUBMIT  
ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION THROUGH THE  
WEBSITES.  
1\. PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE  
1.1 HM and/or its authorised technology agents may collect and store  
certain Personal Information from You in connection with Your use of  
THE WEBSITES and/or the products and/services provided to You by  
HM.  
1.2 For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, Personal Information is defined  
in accordance with the definition in the Act. Generally, such  
information is information that can be used to personally identify you. In  
particular, however, HM may collect information such as:  
1.2.1 first name and surname,  
1.2.2 email address,  
1.2.3 cell phone number,  
1.2.4 profession or occupation,  
from the following persons: any individual who chooses to register on  
THE WEBSITES.  
1.3 HM may also automatically collect and store non-personally identifiable  
information related to your use of the THE WEBSITES. Non-personally  
identifiable information may include personal information that has been  
aggregated.  
1.4 We may share non-personally identifiable information with third parties  
for certain reasons, including advertising, marketing and/or other  
purposes.  
1.5 Your Personal Information is used to provide You with the requested  
products and/or services; enable ease of use of THE WEBSITES;  
process transactions concluded by You; engage in electronic  
communications and transactions with You; administer promotions or  
survey or similar interactive activity; or to provide You with newsletters  
or other periodic communications and/or marketing materials.  
1.6 Personal Information is automatically collected in relation to Your visit  
to THE WEBSITES, such information includes but is not limited to:  
Your browser type and version, as well as Your operating system.  
1.7 Cookies are small files send from THE WEBSITES to a Your computer  
drive that can be used to track when You visit and re-visit a website  
and how you behave on websites. HM may use cookies to identify the  
device with which You access THE WEBSITES and may use  
anonymous cookies to determine website usage analytics and statistics  
in order to optimise THE WEBSITES and Your experience. You are  
able to manually delete cookies from Your browser or set Your browser  
to reject cookies. PLEASE NOTE that certain pages or features may  
not be available or work correctly if You have set Your browser to reject  
cookies.  
1.8 HM uses Google Analytics and Effective Measures, which supports  
data collection without browser cookies. It helps HM to understand user  
interaction with THE WEBSITES and implement changes that evolve  
THE WEBSITES to suit Your needs.  
1.9 The WEBSITES hosting agents and/or service providers may  
automatically log Your “IP address” which is a unique identifier for Your  
computer and/or other access device. Such information collected is for  
aggregate purposes only and cannot be used to identify You  
personally.  
1.10 In the event that You subscribe to newsletters and/or to receive further  
information through other periodic communications, from HM, Your  
Personal Information will be processed by HM to provide You with such  
information and associated processes. All HM communications shall  
contain an unsubscribe link and by following the unsubscribe process  
You shall be removed from the relevant distribution list and HM shall no  
longer send You the subscription information. Should you experience  
any issues with this process please contact our legal advisor, Tracey  
Stewart at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) directly.  
2\. CONSENT TO PROCESS PERSONAL INFORMATION  
2.1 You understand that Your consent to the processing of your personal  
information by HM pertains to the provision of the products and  
services made available on THE WEBSITES; as well as associated  
purposes. Processing shall include the collection, receipt, recording,  
organisation, collation, storage, updating or modification, retrieval,  
alteration, consultation, use; dissemination by means of transmission,  
distribution or making available in any other form; or merging, linking,  
as well as blocking, degradation, erasure or destruction of information.  
2.2 This consent is effective from the moment you access THE WEBSITES  
and will endure until Your access and/or relationship with HM has been  
terminated.  
2.3 You expressly consent to HM retaining Your Personal Information once  
your relationship with HM has been terminated for: aggregate,  
statistical and reporting purposes.  
2.4 In the event that You wish to revoke all consent pertaining to Your  
Personal Information and You would like HM to remove and/or delete  
Your Personal Information entirely, You must notify HM via email to  
HM's legal advisor, Tracey Stewart email address: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
2.5 By Using THE WEBSITES, You represent that You are of the age of 18  
or that a Competent Person has given consent to allow Your minor  
child to utilise THE WEBSITES. You, or a ‘Competent Person’ in the  
case of a minor, consent/s to the processing of personal information  
that belongs to You or, in the case of a minor, to the minor for whom  
You are responsible, in the manner described in this Policy. You agree  
that giving such consent means that You have given HM permission to  
collect and process the child’s personal information in the ways  
described in this Policy.  
3\. HANDLING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
3.1 HM endeavors to comply with all laws and regulations pertaining to  
information and communications privacy including, but not limited to,  
the 1996 South African Constitution and the Protection of Personal  
Information Act 4 of 2013 (“the Act”). HM applies the principles of  
protection of personal information under such Act in further legislation  
referred to in the Act.  
3.2 You have the right to correct Your Personal Information as well as to  
revoke Your consent to the processing of Your Personal Information by  
HM. You do, however, understand that HM requires Your Personal  
Information to render the HM products and/or services and should You  
decide to revoke Your consent HM may not be able to provide You with  
such products and/or services.  
3.3 HM will take all reasonable measures in order to ensure Your Personal  
Information is appropriately safeguarded, these precautions include,  
but are not limited to: the use of a sufficiently secure server and  
providing suitably secure payment mechanisms.  
3.4 Should any unauthorised person/s gain access to Your personal  
information HM will contact You within a reasonable time to inform You  
of the security breach.  
3.5 HM seeks to ensure the quality, accuracy and confidentiality of  
Personal Information in its possession.  
3.6 HM may share Your personal information with authorised third parties  
these include persons such as employees and service providers to HM.  
HM does not permit these parties to use such information for any other  
purpose than to perform the services that HM has instructed them to  
provide and in accordance with this Policy.  
3.7 From time to time, HM may appoint certain agents, third parties and/or  
service providers which operate outside the borders of the Republic of  
South Africa. In these circumstances HM will be required to transmit  
Your Personal Information outside South Africa. The purpose of the  
trans-border flow of Your Personal Information may include, but is not  
limited to: data hosting and storage. You expressly consent to the  
trans-border flow of Your Personal Information. Furthermore, You  
warrant in this regard that You have obtained the necessary consents  
required in terms of the Act, in order to enable the trans-border flow of  
any personal information submitted by You. HM warrants in this regard  
that it shall only engage the services of third parties (in relation to the  
aforesaid trans-border flow of information) which subscribe acceptable  
safeguards in accordance with HM’s legal obligations.  
3.8 HM will not sell, exchange or transfer Your Personal Information to any  
third party except as required in the provision of the HM products  
and/or services and in accordance with the consents provided by You.  
3.9 HM will make amendments and/or updates to this Privacy Policy on  
occasion. Amendments made to this Policy shall become immediately  
effective. We encourage You to periodically review this Policy to keep  
informed about how HM is protecting Your Personal Information. You  
can find the last date of change made to the Policy above for Your  
reference. Your continued Use of THE WEBSITES evidences Your  
acceptance of this Privacy Policy and any updates made to it.  
3.10 THE WEBSITES may contain links to other WEBSITES. HM is not  
responsible for the privacy practices of third party sites.  
4\. DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
4.1 Records relating to the provision of the HM products and/or services by  
HM to You and the Personal Information submitted by You may be  
required to be retained in terms of legislated records retention  
requirements, HM’s operational purposes and/or for production as  
evidence by HM in legal proceedings.  
4.2 HM may disclose Your Personal Information under the following  
circumstances:  
4.2.1 To comply with the law or with legal process;  
4.2.2 To protect and defend HM’s rights, equipment, facilities and other  
property;  
4.2.3 To protect HM against misuse or unauthorised use of THE WEBSITES  
and/or products and/or services; and/or  
4.2.4 To protect other WEBSITES their Users or third parties affected  
negatively by Your actions in use of the products/services and/or THE  
WEBSITES  
5\. OBJECTIONS, COMPLAINTS AND QUERIES  
5.1 Should You require a correction to be made to Your Personal  
Information that HM keeps on record, or a copy of the record itself, or  
should You feel that You would like to object to the collection, Use or  
processing of Your Personal Information by HM, or that you would like  
us to delete your personally identifiable information, then kindly send  
an e-mail to our Information Officer, whose name and details are set  
out below. We will endeavour to make the correction, provide You with  
the record (We reserve our right to charge a small fee in this case),  
cease processing of Your Personal Information and/or delete it, in  
accordance with Your request.  
INFORMATION OFFICER: HM LEGAL ADVISOR – TRACEY STEWART  
EMAIL ADDRESS: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
TEL: 021 416 0141
